[camera clicking]
[Patricia in Yoruba]
I'm going to the police.
[Ishaya in English]
You can't go to the police.
Oga Rambo bribes them.
If they tell him, he'll do something
to Rahila. Please don't go.
[Patricia crying] Ishaya.
[in Yoruba] You are just like your father.
[in English] See how you're destroying
your sister's life to follow your dream.
[sniffles]
Just like your father killed his son,
Dauda, just for the love of art.
Ishaya.
[in Yoruba] Get out of this house.
And don't return
unless it's with your sister.
Get out!
[in English] Mummy, Mummy…
-[Patricia exclaims]
-[grave music playing]
[Rahila whimpering and crying]
Train her so she can dance tomorrow.
Uncle, please!
Uncle, please, I'm begging you with God.
Ijoba.
[in Yoruba] We should have killed the boy
and fed him to Angel.
[Ijoba in English] Take her away.
[sobbing] Uncle, please!
[dramatic music playing]
[cars honking]
-[phone chiming]
-[dramatic music continues]
[bystanders clamoring]
[Ishaya exclaims]
[in Pidgin] Sorry, sir.
I was delayed due to traffic.
[in English] Thank you, sir.
[in Pidgin] Sir, hold on.
This money is not complete.
[in English] Is the picture framed?
-Sir--
-Is it?
[in Pidgin] But this
wasn't the agreement, sir.
[Adufe in Yoruba] Look at this one.
[in English] The pool lights
around the pool.
[in Yoruba] You know what I like?
I liked the way
you played with me all night.
As long as you keep doing that,
-there's nothing I won't buy for you.
-Mmm.
[Joe in Pidgin] Stay there.
[in Pidgin] What happened?
[Joe] Mr. Moscow
says she refuses to dance,
and since Government isn't around,
I brought her to you.
[Oga Rambo in Yoruba] You want me
to teach her how to dance?
[in English] Who is this?
[in Yoruba] She's that thief's sister!
We gave him a job,
but instead he stole from us.
Take her for dance training.
[in English] Uh…
Rambo, she's not Rush's standard.
[in Yoruba] Uh-huh?
She can't dance for Rush.
[Oga Rambo] She looks like a fish.
Keep her in the dungeon for now.
[in Pidgin] Government
said to train her to dance tonight.
[in Yoruba] Are you deaf?
[Joe mutters in English] Will you get…
Will you stand up?
Stand up!
[Rahila whimpering]
I have to go to the salon now.
I have a customer waiting.
[in Yoruba] Let me marry you,
so I can spoil you with money.
[in English] Okay.
I'll think about it.
Adufe.
[in Yoruba] The boss's heart.
Bad girl.
[Ishaya in English]
Michael, I don't know what I will do.
[door opening]
[Adufe] Ishaya.
[in Pidgin] Do you know that
Rahila is in a stripper's uniform at Rush?
Did your boyfriend not kidnap her?
Didn't you steal from him?
[in English] What's the plan?
You have to get her out.
[in Pidgin] Or Government
will have her on drugs in no time.
[Ijoba in English] We need to diversify.
But this,
this will attract rich young people.
[Reggie] Don't be a snitch.
[Ijoba] That's the only way
we can compete today.
[in Pidgin] Selling art in the streets
is not gonna work.
[in English] I'll get another plan.
But
I need you to get me
a meeting with Government.
[in Pidgin] Adufe, please. I beg you.
[in English] Okay.
Come to the club before closing.
[suspenseful music playing]
[house music playing]
[door opening]
-Did anyone touch you?
-[whimpering]
Ishaya will get you out of here. Just eat.
-Don't leave me!
-[Adufe] He's coming soon, don't worry.
Baido, please don't tell anyone
you saw me here.
I swear I'll pay you back.
[tense music playing]
[Ishaya nervously]
See, those rich children in Wilmer,
they will buy your molly
because I can sell it to them.
See, I go there now, see…
See their uniform?
[Oga Rambo] Baido.
[in Yoruba] Feed him to Angel.
-[Ishaya in English] No, wait, please!
-[Ijoba] Stop.
Say more.
[Ishaya] Thank you, sir.
I was in the toilets this morning,
and I saw some children,
they were smoking some type of weed
that I've never smelled before.
Mr. Government, these children,
they have money.
They like expensive things,
they like new things.
Please give me some molly,
let me sell it to them.
I promise, I swear to God, it will work.
[Oga Rambo in Yoruba]
Have you sold before?
Answer me, have you?
Ijoba, are you falling for this?
[in English] Uh, those kids,
they spend millions to party,
and if he goes to the school,
they can trust him and buy--
[in Yoruba] Shut your mouth.
Don't do that again.
Sit down.
[in English] I'll give you
my molly to sell.
But if there's any mistake,
I'll kill him myself.
[Oga Rambo in Yoruba] No.
Angel will kill him.
That's her job.
[tense music playing]
[Ijoba in English] 500,000 naira
worth of Molly.
Sell it in a week.
Sir?
This is more than what I owe you, sir.
Since you can't pay me what you owe me,
I own your life.
Give him his sister.
My number one rule
is to never get high on my supply.
[menacing music playing]
[somber music playing]
[Patricia] Rahila.
Rahila.
[Mr. Bello] My baby.
My baby. Aw.
[Patricia in Yoruba] You can't come in.
-[bittersweet music playing]
-[Mr. Bello mutters]
[in English] So glad you're back.
Ah, I missed my baby.
I missed my baby so much.
[bittersweet music continues]
[Michael in Pidgin] That makes no sense.
Why did you tell Government
you could sell this at Wilmer?
What should I have said?
I don't know, but not this.
[smacks lips] Do you even have the balls
to sell drugs for Government?
I don't have a choice.
[upbeat music playing]
[knocks on door]
[in English] Ishaya,
you've come to visit me!
Uh, actually, we're roommates.
I thought I was going to be alone.
No one showed up yesterday.
[laughing] Whoa, okay.
-[bell ringing]
-[upbeat music continues]
You should take a picture.
It will last longer.
I'm here to see Ms. Irurhe.
I just wanted to ask her
about the London art competition thing.
How about you?
-Planning Founder's Day ball.
-Which one is that one?
An event where parents dress formal,
drink champagne,
in the name of our founding father.
I can introduce you to a few millionaires
if you join the planning committee.
[chuckles] Okay.
I'll join.
Sorry about that.
Uh, where are you going?
Ishaya offered to take my place
on the planning committee.
Have fun.
[Ms. Irurhe] Okay, Ishaya.
Um, let's get started after lunch.
[upbeat music playing]
[in Pidgin] Why didn't you get this thing?
[in English] It's a shrimp wrap.
I'm allergic to seafood.
[Ishaya] Shrimp wrap.
[in Pidgin] Food's good, right?
It's good. It's actually good.
-[in English] Ishaya, are you on Blink?
-[Ishaya] Yeah.
[phone chimes]
Party this weekend. You ready?
-Those guys, are they on Blink too?
-[Frank] Yeah.
Coke go choke.
Take a look.
[in Pidgin] Wow, who's this Reggie guy?
[in English] Captain of the football team,
son of Senator Flag-Kukrubo.
-And a tall glass of hot chocolate.
-[Ishaya] Okay.
I heard he's having a party
at his house this weekend.
-But you have to be invited.
-How do I get invited?
Be cool
or be a member of the football team.
Tryouts are tomorrow.
Tryouts?
Guy, download the school app.
[intriguing music playing]
[whistle blows]
I see some of you new boys
looking at me and thinking to yourselves,
"Isn't this the Okeke Tony
who used to play for the Super Eagles?"
Well, I can tell you for free
that, yes, I am he.
[chuckles] Mmm-hmm.
Mmm-hmm.
Mmm-mmm.
You can't play without boots,
shin pads, and hoses.
Go to the lost and found
and get something.
[upbeat music playing]
[players muttering and laughing]
Let's play ball!
[whistle blows]
[coach] If you do not jump for the ball,
you cannot get the header!
[whistle blows]
-All right, let's play ball!
-[whistle blows]
[upbeat music continues]
Pass!
Pass the ball!
Pass! Pass!
Shoot! Shoot!
Yes!
New boy! Welcome to the team, new boy!
Reggie, give him a warm welcome.
-Baller.
-Hey.
-Nice one, bro.
-Thanks, man.
Hey, we're about to head over
to the cheerleading tryouts.
-Wanna come?
-Sure.
-All right.
[upbeat music continues]
You're in.
Next.
[Nen] Zina.
[Ishaya] Bro, that's my friend.
Go, Zina! Go, Zina!
[Nen] Hey, here's your uniform.
Let me see that.
Nen, you know this is a cheer squad,
not a choir, right?
My mum wants us to look decent.
[huffs] Start, please.
[hip-hop music playing]
[Ishaya] Go, Zina.
[whispers] That's my friend.
-[mouths] Oh, yeah!
-[hip-hop music continues]
-[music stops suddenly]
-[all groaning]
[Nen] This is not a music video audition.
But she was amazing!
She's clearly not cheer squad material.
She'll be a distraction.
Which we'll need when
we wear these nun's uniforms.
[Ishaya] Zina! Zina!
-Zina! Zina! Zina!
-[all cheering and whooping]
Okay, fine!
She's in.
-Yes!
-[Zina] Yes!
Hey, I'm having a party
at mine this weekend.
Bring your friend.
[Nen] Carmen, you're up next.
What?
-You're next.
-I was cheer squad captain last year.
Well, I'm cheer squad captain now.
Okay?
[Zina] Guess who got
invited to Reggie's party?
Please make videos so I get
to live vicariously through you guys.
-[both] Which one is vicariously?
-[both laughing]
-[Zina] What am I going to wear?
-Hey.
[in Pidgin] See, dude, I don't have
any time for your problems right now.
Please.
-[in English] You want me to tell them--
-Tell them what?
See, guys, just go ahead,
I'll catch up with you later, okay?
[in Pidgin] Yes?
[in English] I want to follow you
to Reggie's party.
"I want to follow you to Reggie's party."
[in Pidgin] Am I your dad?
Go away, please.
[upbeat music playing]
[Michael] How will you
sell it at the party?
I don't know. I'll give it to Reggie
to sell to his friends.
[banging on door]
[banging continues]
[Michael] Rahila.
-You decided to steal my dream from me?
-[Michael] It wasn't like that.
He's only there
so he can save you from Oga Rambo.
[in English] Whose fault was it
that I got kidnapped in the first place?
You're always so selfish.
How could you do this to me?
[melancholy music playing]
[door opens and closes]
[Mrs. Willoughby] Carmen? Nnenna's here!
I'm only allowing her to go to this party
because of you.
I trust your judgement to keep her safe.
I hope you're not here
to ask me to repeat tryouts.
And I hope you realize
that I am cheer captain, not you.
I was only helping.
If making me look weak as fuck
is you helping,
just keep that shit to yourself.
Well, now I know what I have to do
to get you to come over,
and it's not
getting into a life-threatening accident.
You weren't there when I needed you.
I didn't mean
not to come over and see you.
It's just
school, and church, and…
There's no excuse.
I've been a total bitch.
I should have come over and see you.
[sighs] I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to disrespect you
as cheer captain.
[laughing] Come here.
I missed you.
Thank God you're here,
because I have nothing to wear.
Don't tell me you're going to
the pool party dressed like your mother.
[Carmen] Easy for you to say.
Your leg doesn't look like this.
I can't get plastic surgery
until the plates are out.
You know what? Fuck the scar.
Wear a bikini.
No one will notice when
they're looking at, you know, all of this.
-You know you have it.
-Nen, stop. No.
Come on, let's get you something to wear.
Stop being…
[dance music playing]
[blows into mic] All right, people.
I'd like us to give a big welcome back to…
-Carmen!
-[all whooping]
[all cheering]
[upbeat music continues]
Babe.
How was the lawyer's?
It was great.
He didn't think I was his?
[angrily] Did my father
tell you he didn't think I was his son?
[objects clatter]
Atlas, thank God you're here.
She won't take off her scarf,
or swim, or dance.
Maybe you can loosen her up.
I need to have some fun.
Bye.
-Yo, Ishaya.
-Hey.
-How's it?
-It's popping, man.
-Aren't you gonna introduce us?
-I think we know each other's names.
I mean, what I don't know
is how long it's gonna take you
to have those shorts off.
Okay! Ha!
[guest] Cheers!
Babe…
I think this party's a bad idea.
-I'm not comfortable.
-[sighs]
-My scar--
-Again with this, your scar talk!
Excuse me?
Carmen, I don't have
time for this shit today, okay?
[Reggie] What do you mean, "sold out"?
I promised people molly.
[in Pidgin] What if you
get caught by the police? It's a crime.
Please think of a better way.
[in English] Better way?
[in Pidgin] What better way?
[upbeat music playing]
[in English] Ugh, fuck off.
Dude, dude, uh…
See this? This is top-grade shit.
Ten K per pill.
Let me see.
Bro, how do I know
you didn't cook this in a kitchen?
Are you buying or not?
All right.
Pop one.
[in Yoruba] Pop, why?
[in English] If it's as good as you say,
I'll buy.
-This…
-Hey, it's cool.
[Ishaya] Wait.
Whoa, whoa. Chill, chill. Um…
I'll pop it.
See you in an hour.
[dark hip-hop music playing]
Mmm! Okay!
-Is it good?
-To be honest, this is good.
Magic hands, what can I say?
Is that what they do?
You have no idea
what these hands do, babe.
[Zina laughing] What, like…
beat up people for me?
If you need me to.
Oh, my days, you're so cheesy.
Ah!
I'll take some of that, bro.
-Really?
-Mmm-hmm.
[chuckles] Okay.
Yeah.
-I'll sort you out later?
-Water.
Kitchen.
Down the hallway, to the right.
[phone ringing]
Ijoba.
[Ijoba] It's the end of the week.
Where are you?
[in Pidgin] I'm at a party.
Do you want to come around?
I will send the address to you.
[grunts]
Hey.
Mmm!
[in English] Why?
You asked to take the picture
of the most beautiful girl in school.
Hmm?
Okay.
[Ishaya] Okay. Okay.
Hey!
-Oh, what's that?
-[grunts]
Why are you hiding it?
Shh. I want to show you something.
What are you doing?
See this?
It's from when I stole oranges
from my neighbors.
This…
I broke my principal's windscreen.
[in Pidgin] They flogged me.
-[Ishaya] Oh…
-[romantic music playing]
[in English] Car accident.
I was driving.
[Ishaya] Scars reflect
who you are as a person.
You shouldn't hide it.
Here, let me show you this.
See this one? Come feel it.
You can't see it,
just feel it.
-[romantic music stops]
-I need to go find my boyfriend.
[upbeat music playing]
Pizza!
[upbeat music continues]
I've missed this.
Frank.
[in Pidgin] Take a look at the house.
[laughs]
[in English] Living vicariously, you said?
Oh!
-[Atlas] What the…
-Shit!
Shit, shit, shit!
Enjoy.
-Why didn't you lock the door?
-I thought you did.
-[Atlas] Was he recording?
-I don't know!
Go after him, what are you doing?
[upbeat music continues]
[Mrs. Willoughby] Where are we
going this year?
-[woman] France.
-[door opens]
-[Carmen] Auntie!
-[woman] Oh!
-[Carmen] Mmm!
-Darling!
[Carmen] Mama!
Mama, hug.
-[grunts]
-Stop.
-[whining] Mama, give me a hug!
-Stop. Stop it.
[Carmen] Auntie!
-Auntie, I missed you!
-[Atlas] I can explain, Auntie.
Uh, when I found… Carmen.
[Nen] She disappeared.
And by the time we found her,
she was drunk.
Leave me.
You will not fail to embarrass me.
I guess I should be grateful
you didn't drive.
[slurring] Mum,
enough with this accident talk!
It wasn't even my fault. I wasn't the one…
[yelps]
-I'm really sorry, Auntie.
-[yelps]
Carmen, upstairs.
I love you, Mama.
Atlas, leave me alone!
[Atlas mutters]
Sorry.
[woman snickers] That's more drunk
than I've ever been in my life.
[Mrs. Willoughby scoffs] Children!
[laughs nervously]
[animal panting]
[growls]
[gasping]
[in Yoruba] Jesus. I'm in trouble.
Jesus.
[in English] My number one rule
is to never get high on my supply.
-Brother Government.
-Where are my pills?
[in Yoruba] I'm dead!
-[in English] It's with Reggie…
-Where's my money?
[Ishaya] That's what I'm saying,
just let me call…
[Oga Rambo in Yoruba] Hey!
My Angel will eat your head first.
[in Pidgin] God save me.
Brother Government, Brother Government,
Brother Government!
[in Yoruba] Angel, your food is here.
Please think of a better way!
[in English] Please, please!
[in Yoruba] I'm not Government.
I don't forgive.
Do you understand?
[cage opens]