[camera clicking]
[lounge music playing]
[cameras clicking]
[woman] Ladies and gentlemen,
we are live at the grand opening
of Ishaya Bello's first art exhibition.
[all cheering and clapping]
[Ishaya] Thank you.
Thank you all for coming.
Who would have thought
that the dreams of a young boy…
[in Yoruba]
…from Lagos Island would become this?
I always dreamt of being an artist,
of being Essien,
and I got a chance to work with him
as an apprentice in London,
and, boy, he changed my life.
Thank you, Essien.
-[all clapping]
-[Ishaya] Thank you.
Also I'd like to thank my friends.
[woman] Ishaya.
Ishaya, wake up!
You're late for work.
Mum is waiting outside. She's very angry.
Shit.
-Shit, shit, shit!
-[expectant music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[Patricia in Yoruba]
Ishaya, we are already late.
Will you stop dragging your feet?
[expectant music playing]
[man in English] Right.
Hello.
Who are you again?
I'm the cleaner, sir.
Madam Patricia's son.
Oh.
Okay.
[expectant music continues]
[upbeat music playing]
Sister, fine drawing
for your wall, ma, for your wall.
-I painted it myself, it's original. Ma!
-[woman] I don't want.
[Ishaya] Mama, do you like paintings?
Mama, painting for your fine wall
in your house.
I painted it by myself, ma.
It's a fine work.
Sir, you can buy this drawing.
I drew it myself.
It's original work from me, sir! Sir!
Sir! Daddy, help me now.
[Michael in Pidgin]
Why are you so eager to sell your art?
I need money quickly.
[in English] Money for what?
Ishaya.
[in Pidgin] What's going on?
[in English] Nothing.
[in Pidgin] Have you got someone pregnant?
You'll get someone pregnant, idiot.
Okay, talk to me, what's going on?
Tell me.
[in English] You know that…
[in Pidgin] That artist from London?
Essien, your role model.
Essien. He has this art fellowship…
to study with him for six months.
I applied.
You applied?
He picked me.
-[in English] Yeah?
-I swear.
He actually picked me.
[in Pidgin] Don't lie.
Let me see your face. You're lying.
Why would I lie?
I said he picked… Come see the video.
[Michael] No way.
[in English] Dear Ishaya,
if you're watching this video…
[in Pidgin] Look.
[in English] …then congratulations.
You have been selected
as one of my apprentices in London.
You'll get the required training,
expertise,
and exposure to start your career
on the global stage.
[in Pidgin] Wow, my guy, you did it!
-How come you didn't tell me?
-Shh! Quiet.
-You're traveling to London?
-That's what I'm trying to arrange.
Before you say "Jack Robinson," you'll be
in London sipping tea with the Queen.
Jack Robinson. Jack Robinson.
Am I in London now?
[Michael] Calm down. You'll go to London.
My clients will buy your artwork.
-[Ishaya] Upfront.
-Upfront. Before!
Let me take a bath
and get ready for Rahila's birthday party.
-What?
-[Ishaya] Shit, I haven't bought the cake.
-[Ishaya] Shit, shit, shit.
This guy…
[upbeat music playing]
-[in English] What are you doing here?
-Go and sit down.
[in Yoruba] Okay?
[in Pidgin] Rahila, your cake is here.
-[Ishaya in English] Babe!
-[Michael] Happy birthday!
Hi! Wait till you see what I got.
I bought it for Rahila.
-[in Pidgin] What is this?
-Come on, Ishaya.
[in English] It's trendy.
[in Pidgin] So she will attract friends.
I don't want these for her,
looks like clothes for a prostitute.
-It's not bad, I like it.
-I know you'll like this. Naughty!
-[in English] Thank you.
-[both muttering and laughing]
Good day sir.
[Adufe] Let's play.
[all exclaiming]
All right, come and eat.
[groans]
Are you OK?
[in Yoruba] Want to go to the bedroom?
[mouthing]
[Adufe in English] Rahila,
your dream school advert is on.
[woman on TV] At Wilmer Academy,
we are all about giving back
to the society that raised us.
Do you want to win a scholarship
to the most prestigious School in Nigeria?
For those of you who want to come
to Wilmer Academy, here's your chance.
Come to the Wilmer Academy Open Day
and register for the scholarship exam,
and maybe you'll be the--
Hey, now, Mummy, I was watching it!
[in Yoruba] Don't waste your time.
Attending that school is a futile dream.
You hear me?
[downbeat music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[in English] My dear daughter,
today's your birthday, hmm?
Let's be merry.
[in Yoruba] Did you hear? Don't frown.
Go and eat.
[in English] Birthday girl.
[Michael in Pidgin] Smile. That looks…
[in English] ♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
[all] ♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Lala ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Thank you.
[in Pidgin] You know
I can't draw your dream every day.
[in English] Chase it now
so you don't regret it later.
My dreams are too expensive.
Plus, I don't even think I belong there.
Unrealistic dreams are destructive.
-Know what I think?
-What?
[in Pidgin] Tomorrow is their Open Day,
right?
-[in English] Go there.
-Hmm?
Register for the scholarship exam.
I mean, you never know.
Mmm-mmm.
[grunts]
[in Yoruba] Shame.
[in English] Will you follow me?
[in Yoruba] I'm busy, please.
[in English] Please, now.
Look, I'm too busy following
my own dreams.
[in Yoruba] Did you hear?
[in English] Okay, I'll follow you.
["Triumphant" by
Olamide ft. Bella Shmurda playing]
[in Pidgin] Don't you have a shirt?
Why are you wearing that shirt?
Tsk.
[in Yoruba] Are you now
ashamed of where Lagos Island?
[in English] Let's go.
[in Yoruba] Please leave me alone.
-["Triumphant" continues playing]
-[phone chiming]
["Triumphant" continues playing]
[phone chiming]
-[car honking]
-[Ishaya] Lala!
[man muttering]
[in Yoruba] Gutter trash
who've never seen wealth before.
[in Pidgin] Riff-raff. Drive on.
[in Yoruba] Just look at them. Rubbish.
[song fading]
Didn't I tell you
not to wear this shirt?
[woman in English] Welcome.
I'd like to sign up
for the scholarship exam.
Fill this form.
Pay the registration fee of 150,000 naira.
150,000?
For a scholarship exam?
The entry exam is not free.
But it is a scholarship.
Don't you want to give it to someone
that can't actually afford to pay?
Can she write the exam now and pay for it
later when she gets the scholarship?
[woman] This is Wilmer Academy…
[in Yoruba] …not Lagos Island
Secondary School.
[in English] It's fine, Lala. Let's go.
Let's go.
You look absolutely ravishing.
Your smile lights up the entire room.
-[scoffs] Please, sit down.
-Thank you.
[Rahila] Dreaming is destructive.
My dreams are unrealistic.
[Ishaya] Lala, that doesn't
even make sense.
No, look at Daddy.
[in Pidgin] Dad wanting to be
a famous artist lost us our brother.
Now he's in pain every time.
[in English] Maybe Daddy
will actually stop being in pain
if he starts doing what he loves,
just painting.
That's why, me, I'm chasing my dream.
Lala, just because
you can't get into Wilmer
doesn't mean you can't be the neuro…
whatever doctor you decide you want to be.
Wilmer is not the only school in Lagos.
It's neurosurgeon.
You shut up your dirty mouth.
[sniffles]
["Blessings" by Niphkeys
and Zinoleesky playing loudly]
["Blessings" continues playing]
Go, go, go!
[song fading]
[in Yoruba] What did he do?
[in English] He broke my number-one rule.
Got high on my supply.
[in Yoruba] That's a serious offense.
Baido, feed him to Angel.
[man] Baido, feed him to Angel.
[exhales]
[in English] Joe.
Sir, um…
[in Pidgin] The weed is selling, but…
this medicine is not.
[in English] Molly or ecstasy, Joe.
[in Pidgin] You need to know the name.
[in English] Ijoba, Rush is our business.
[in Yoruba] Why are you selling pills?
[in English] We need to diversify.
This will attract rich young people.
[in Pidgin] You and I
know this business is not new.
[Ijoba in English] I will continue
to develop new markets.
[in Yoruba] You're losing your mind,
Government.
[in English] Sell the pills, Joe,
or don't come back.
-[pills clatter]
-[menacing music playing]
What?
My salary, sir.
[Patricia in Yoruba] He's still in pain.
[nurse on phone] Bring him in.
[in English] But you have
to pay your bills before we treat him.
[man groans in English] Oh, no.
Pick up, now.
[line ringing]
-[somber music playing]
-[man groaning]
[phone vibrating]
[cars honking]
[neighbor in Yoruba] Sorry about your dad.
[Ishaya in English] Daddy! Mummy! Lala!
Lala.
It's still the same pain,
but it was worse this time around,
so we had to rush him to the hospital.
[Ishaya in Yoruba] Why didn't you call me?
[Rahila in English] You didn't pick up.
[Ishaya] How much
do we owe the hospital now?
[in Yoruba] Speak up.
Ha.
[Patricia in English] Ishaya…
The medicine they said
we should buy for your father,
that we couldn't afford…
I've bought them.
And the remaining money,
we'll use it for our house rent.
Mummy, please give me back my money.
Mummy, this is the money
for the apprenticeship in London.
The money I need to use to travel.
Mummy, please, just give me
back the rest of my money. Please.
Ishaya, you are wicked.
With all we are going through
in this family,
-you want to travel?
-Please.
-To where?
-London.
To do what? Draw?
[in Yoruba] The devil's work!
[in Pidgin] Isn't it the same evil money
you are using to treat him?
-Give me my money.
-[in Yoruba] How dare you talk that way!
[in English] Give back my money!
[softly] Take it easy.
[Ishaya] It's for three months now!
Just three months!
[in Yoruba] Get out of my sight.
[in Pidgin] Lala, you did this to me?
Why did the ambulance come?
[somber music playing]
[knock on door]
[Michael in Pidgin] Who's that?
How are you, Adufe?
[Adufe] I'm fine, how are you?
[in English] Rahila told me what happened.
I'm sorry.
[Michael in Pidgin]
How would you go about it?
I will go to London.
London? Osapa London in Lekki?
[Michael chuckles]
My guy, you must be kidding.
You neither have a passport nor visa…
And you don't even have enough
for the ticket yet.
[scoffs] I'll find a way.
I'm not going to end up like my father,
sad because I have forsaken my dreams.
Look at Essien.
He saw my work, liked it, and chose me.
[Adufe] Ishaya…
You're planning to leave the country
and didn't tell me?
[Adufe] Ugh.
I thought we would get married.
-I can't marry anybody like this.
-"Anybody"?
[scoffs] I have to succeed first.
So I'm anybody?
Babe, that's not what I said.
-I didn't mean it that way.
-Bless you.
[in English] Babe…
Adufe…
[door slams]
[somber music playing]
["Sungba" by Asake playing]
["Sungba" continues playing]
Oga Rambo wants to see you
in his VIP spot.
[man in Yoruba] Yo, Oluwadollar.
[sighs]
-[song fading]
-[dark music playing]
What the king doesn't have…
he wants.
What does the queen want?
[in English] Open it.
[in Yoruba] Are you deaf?
[in English] Open it!
[in Yoruba] Move it.
[in English] Yes, sir.
[in Yoruba] Ishaya, get up.
Time to go to work.
[phone chimes]
-[somber music playing]
-[phone chimes]
[downbeat music playing]
Check out this gold bracelet
and her choke necklace.
[in Pidgin] Don't choke her too much.
[both laughing]
[in Yoruba] Hey, boy, change some dollars
for me, I need more money, okay?
[in Pidgin] Check
that place for the money.
[man 1 in Yoruba] Bring me this money.
It'd better be complete.
[man 2] No sleep for strippers.
[man 1] Dollar does not depreciate, yeah.
[Oga Rambo] Dollar Boy! Bring me liquor!
[Adufe in English] Ishaya.
Wait.
[in Pidgin] What's up?
You and Oga Rambo?
What's wrong with you?
What do you think you're doing?
You don't get to ask me that
after you treated me like that.
-Huh?
-How did I treat you?
[scoffs]
[in English] See, for your information,
Oga Rambo, he has treated me
better than you ever did, you hear me?
[in Pidgin] Have you ever asked me
what I want out of life?
You don't think I deserve it, but I do.
[in English] Rubbish.
[Ishaya] Sir, a customer
wants to change money.
Get ten bundles, put it in that bag.
Nine, ten.
[Ijoba] We need
new market for the molly ASAP.
[Essien on video] You have been selected
as one of my apprentices in London.
[Ishaya] Look, I'm too busy
following my own dreams.
-[tense music playing]
-[whines]
[bills clatter]
Will it take you a million years
to count ten fucking bundles?
Sorry. Sorry, sir. I'm done.
[menacing music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[music stops]
[in Yoruba] You're obsessed with music.
All day long, it's music! Why?
[in English] Here.
What's this?
Wilmer entrance exam answers.
But, Daddy, I can pass it on my own.
One thing I've always wanted,
to be the managing director
of Five Star Realty,
selling mansions to billionaires.
And you know where those billionaires are?
Wilmer Academy.
I need you to memorize those answers,
get in,
help me get rich.
With a scholarship,
there's no school fees.
And $10,000 award.
So, cram those answers.
Capisce?
Capisce.
[exclaims softly]
[intriguing music playing]
Sorry, sir.
Cleaner boy, wait!
I threw something away by mistake.
Open the bag.
What are you looking for now?
Shut up. Don't ask such stupid questions.
-[Ishaya] Lala.
-Hmm?
What if I told you I had the answers
to Wilmer entrance exams?
100% guaranteed,
you'd get the scholarship.
I still don't have the money for the test.
What if I told you
I had the money for the test too?
I don't think
I want to go there by cheating.
It only means I don't deserve to be there,
so, no.
[in Pidgin] You know how much
the top student wins?
How much? A million?
Six million.
Look at you,
I've already registered with 150,000.
Where'd you get the money?
Why are you stealing Rahila's dream?
I asked her, she said
she won't cheat to achieve her dream.
[in English] Me,
I'll do anything to get my dream.
[in Pidgin] Understand?
Here, help me learn the answers.
[in English] Number one, B.
Number two, C. Number three…
Thirty-eight, D. Thirty-nine…
Forty-one, C.
[intriguing music playing]
[woman] You have 90 minutes.
You may begin.
[intriguing music continues]
[woman] Face forward.
[indistinct chatter on TV]
-[phone chimes]
-[chatter continues loudly on TV]
-[commentator on TV] It's a goal!
-[cheering on TV]
[exclaiming]
[spectators clamoring]
[Michael exclaiming] My guy!
[man] Get out!
The best education in Africa.
Thank you for choosing Wilmer Academy.
What do you think?
I think that was pretty good.
You're coming, right?
I have to go to church with my mom,
but I'll come over later.
Okay?
-Good luck! Bye!
-Ugh.
[tense music playing]
[woman on PA] The Wilmer Academy
Open Day is a proud tradition
that goes back 20 years,
where our leaders of tomorrow experience
Wilmer for the first time as scholars.
After registration,
please make your way into the auditorium,
where the program will commence.
Thank you.
Excuse me a second.
Ishaya Bello?
I am Principal Gemade.
[muffled] Pleased to meet you, ma'am.
[laughs dryly]
[sighs] I'll see you after the tour.
[muttering angrily] Stuffing your face…
Principal Gemade, meet my son.
-Oh!
-[intriguing music playing]
I'm sorry,
Carmen.
Next time,
don't touch,
Ishaya.
-Mum.
-Where have you been?
-I--
-Here. Your speech.
Just read it like you mean it.
Here.
Smile. Let's go.
[Gemade] And I know this year will be
one of the best years
Wilmer Academy has ever seen.
[Gemade] Without further ado,
I'd like to call on
the great-granddaughter of the founder
to welcome her fellow students
to the new academic year.
Good afternoon.
My name is Carmen Wilmer Willoughby.
-I'm a descendant of the founding father.
-This babe is fine!
Sorry, but I don't see it.
It's an honor to welcome you all
to the new academic session.
And anyone who dates Atlas
is definitely not a good person.
Atlas?
What, like the map of the world?
Thank you.
[Gemade] Now, before the tour,
I'd like to introduce someone special.
This year,
we started a scholarship program,
which is sponsored by Pastor Okolo.
[all clapping]
Allow me to introduce
the first recipient
who had a perfect score.
Ishaya Bello.
[all clapping]
[dark music playing]
[Frank] I can't believe
you're the scholarship student.
I came second in the exam.
We need to talk.
Hey. You want a picture
with the scholarship student, right?
Come back, I'm busy.
-How dare you!
-[Carmen clears throat]
Can I have your attention?
[Ishaya] Let's go.
[Atlas] Put this thing
on the wall properly now.
-That's now how you--
-[Carmen] Atlas! Hey, babe.
[Atlas] Hey.
[Carmen laughing]
-[Atlas] How are you?
-I'm okay.
-[Atlas] How's the tour going?
-Frustrating.
Guys, this is--
Frankincense!
Is that you I smell?
Atlas, we're too old for this.
Come on, babe.
He clearly missed me.
That's why he followed me
all the way to Wilmer, right?
My name is… I'm Frank.
Yes, but the full thing
is Frankincense, right?
-Frankincense--
-[Ishaya] Hey, hey.
[in Pidgin] Madam Tour Guide,
can we focus on why we're here?
[in English] Or is your boyfriend
what we're here to see?
Let's go.
FYI, the name is Carmen.
And it's this way.
Put this thing on the wall properly now.
And this is the brand-new art gallery.
[ethereal music playing]
[Patricia] You drew this?
I want to be an artist, Mummy, like Daddy.
[Patricia] But you know
art is forbidden in this house.
Daddy! Daddy!
Let me guess. Artist.
How did you know?
You really need to learn
how not to touch without permission.
This way.
[upbeat music playing]
Ma, my $10,000.
Can I get it now?
As soon as we receive your transcript
from your secondary school.
Transcript?
School resumes next week Monday,
so please bring it to us by then.
[man] I thought you were so stupid
you couldn't memorize the answers,
but you're even more stupid,
'cause you threw it away, and now
the cleaner's son got the scholarship.
I wanted to prove
that I could do it on my own.
You are an idiot if you think anyone can
achieve anything honestly in this world!
[in Yoruba] Get out of my sight!
[in English] Get the hell out of my sight.
Nonsense.
[in Yoruba] Just look at him.
-[in English] Hey, Patricia.
-Hello, sir.
You are fired!
Sir, please…
Go and ask that thief you call a son.
[Ishaya in Pidgin]
Bro AB, I know I owe you money.
Please, just let me run this package.
[in English] Whatever it is,
my answer is no.
[in Pidgin] My guy, please,
this is very important.
-I said no!
-[Michael] Guy, calm down!
Please, it's just this document
I need help with.
Replace her name with mine.
-[AB] It'll cost 50K.
-Jesus!
50K is too much for this!
[AB mutters]
[AB in English] Wait.
[Ishaya in Pidgin] I don't have 50K.
[somber music playing]
[in English] Take.
[in Pidgin] I'm pleading with you,
as soon as you get the scholarship money,
return it,
because it's my office contribution.
-I don't want problems.
-Mike…
I beg you in the name of God.
[in English] Thank you.
Thank you.
[upbeat music playing]
[Atlas] Mum, this is the tenth time
I'm calling you. Call me back.
I can't apply for the London Art Institute
grant if my school fees aren't paid.
I can't keep living at Reggie's house.
It's like I'm homeless.
Call me back.
No! Ugh!
[man in Yoruba] Baby.
Can you imagine
that useless man named Allen…
-Uh-huh?
-[in English] You know, his school
is now participating
in the London Art Institute grant?
-I thought that was exclusive to us.
-Apparently not.
[Atlas] Good morning.
-[Mrs. Willoughby] Oh, Atlas!
-I see you have a new Essien on your wall.
One day very soon, we'll have
an Atlas original when you win the grant.
[both chuckling]
-[maid] Miss Carmen.
-What?
Your friend has come
to carry you to school, so Mummy said--
Tell Mummy to come now!
-You mean I should tell her--
-Tell her to come now!
[Mrs. Willoughby] Uh, excuse me.
[maid whispers]
Mmm, okay, okay, uh…
-I'll be right back.
-[Mr. Willoughby] Oh, dear.
So, Atlas, how's your mother?
Uh, she's good.
Good.
[Mrs. Willoughby] What's going on here?
Give it to me!
You don't need any more painkillers.
Only people in pain need it.
Even Dr. Olaoye says you don't need pills.
-It's been a year--
-Neither you nor her shattered your leg!
[Mrs. Willoughby] Enough!
People are watching,
waiting for you to have a breakdown.
You're a Wilmer Willoughby, my daughter.
So chin up and smile!
It feels like
I have no control over my life.
She even took my painkillers.
I don't get it.
Is it her pain? Ugh.
I can't wait to leave this house.
Babe, take it easy.
In two years,
you and I'll be eating caviar
and drinking champagne along the Thames.
[Carmen] Hmm.
Okay.
Thank you.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
-Mum! Finally! I've been trying to--
-[woman] Hello, Atlas.
Your mother is still in Paris.
She'll give you a call later.
[hip-hop music playing]
-Babe, are you okay? What's wrong?
-[tires squealing]
[engine revving]
[hip-hop music continues]
[tires squealing]
-[Carmen gasping]
-[siren wailing]
-[engine revving]
-[shrieks] Atlas, stop!
[car decelerating]
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, baby.
I have to get someone
to call your school's records office
to verify this.
Verify?
The thing is,
the school, their phone lines are down.
So they gave me, um, a phone number
that you can call
in case you need to verify.
Sorry. Just write it down for you here.
[busy signal beeping]
[keypad clicking]
[car honking]
[busy signal beeping]
-This guy. Fuckin' pick up.
-[line ringing]
If it isn't the royal couple
of Wilmer Academy.
Car, you ready for your
welcome back party this weekend?
Why? Oh, my bad! It was a surprise?
[laughs] Surprise.
[Atlas] Babe,
I can cancel if it's too much.
[sighs] No. It's probably what I need.
[Nen] Yes, Mummy.
May God be with you too
as we accomplish His new mission.
Amen.
Crazy.
Now that we are all gathered together,
I have a very special
"Welcome back to Wilmer"
package just for you, Car.
-[Nen] Where's that?
-To the shrine?
[laughs] Mmm, to the shrine!
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
-[knocking]
-[man] Occupied. Fuck off!
[woman giggles]
Bro, this shit smells different.
Yeah, man, I got the Holy Grail of kush
all for Car's first day.
[Atlas laughing]
Step outside, please.
Ma?
My secretary has your uniforms
and schedule.
The transcript?
Verified.
[phone chiming]
Um, so, my prize money, where is it?
-You mean the grant.
-Yes.
You can collect it at the end of the day
from the bursar.
Oh, thank you.
Car, baby, no.
You should know better.
Good thing secondhand smoking is a thing,
so just breathe in, Car, baby.
-[smacks lips]
-[Nen] So what's your problem?
If this is about last week,
I told you, I had a church thing.
Nen, this is about the last few months,
and a quick puff-puff-pass
is not going to fix it.
Can you guys please not fuck up my high?
Exactly.
Let's just go to class.
Is that shit because
I'm a year behind now?
Good God, Carmen. Reggie, please,
light one up for this girl.
She needs to chill.
Babe, you think
maybe it's because of the pills?
What pills?
[Carmen scoffs]
[upbeat music playing]
[Reggie] Fuck.
[Atlas] Leave.
-Are you deaf? I said get the--
-[Nen] Hey, let's go.
Hey, don't be a snitch.
Just for today.
[teacher] Simile, metaphor…
Can I help you?
Um…
I'm Ishaya Bello.
I'm new.
Everyone is,
and no one else is late, Mr. Scholarship.
Can you get somewhere to sit?
As I was saying,
alliteration, irony.
Who can tell me the ninth one?
I have listed eight out of nine…
[upbeat music continues]
[bell ringing]
Do you like Carmen?
You were drawing her.
[laughs] Um…
Here.
-For helping me tie my tie.
-[woman exclaims] Oh, my God.
You drew this in 40 minutes?
Well, 20, actually.
Hi.
I'm Zina. I know you're Ishaya.
And you are?
I'm Denrele.
-I wasn't talking to you.
-Me?
I'm Frank. Frank Abok.
[Zina] Hi, it's nice to meet you guys.
Today we're going to discuss
the plans for the semester,
so no need for your pencils.
This year we're also doing
something very different
for the London Art Institute grant.
Now, everyone can participate,
but only three students,
one from your year and
two from the second year,
will be submitting
directly to the London Art Institute.
Now, to select the students,
I will be giving you all an assignment.
Deadline is next Thursday.
You're very talented.
I look forward to seeing
your submission for the shortlist.
I don't think I'll be submitting anything.
After removing the cost
of books and uniform,
your balance is now 5,000 naira.
Sir?
Five thousand what?
[somber music playing]
[phone vibrating]
[in Pidgin] Michael,
I was given 5,000 naira.
[crying]
I was given 5,000 naira, what do I do?
What do I do?
[somber music continues]
[Ishaya in English] Jesus.
[Ijoba in Yoruba] Don't you know
I'm from the streets?
[in English] Rambo's family…
took me in and raised me.
When his mother died,
we were left on our own,
hustling on the streets.
You can ask your father,
who knew us before we started our business
that earned us our respect.
Then you have the…
temerity…
to steal 150,000 naira from us.
[Patricia] Huh?
[in Yoruba] You think we are so stupid
that we don't have cameras
in the money room?
[in English] Brother Government,
Brother Rambo, please, I'll pay you--
[Patricia yelps]
[in Pidgin] Please, I'll pay you back,
I just need a little time.
Please, a little time--
[Ijoba in Yoruba] Government,
Angel is hungry.
Let's feed him to her.
-[both exclaim]
-[man] Uh, Kasali--
[Oga Rambo] Don't call me that!
That's not my name.
[in English] I'm sorry, Oga Rambo.
Please. I beg you.
[Ishaya sobs in Pidgin] I'll pay you back,
I just need just a little time.
[in English] Please. Please.
Please. Please, sir. Please.
You have one week.
Or your sister will clear your debt
in our private rooms.
No. No, take me, I'll follow you.
Leave my daughter.
[in Yoruba] Woman, no man
will pay anything to look at you.
[Ishaya in Pidgin] Please, please,
I'll pay the money. I just need time.
[Rahila sobs in English] We'll pay your
money back, sir, please.
Mummy, don't let them take me! Leave me!
-[shrieks] Leave me! Leave me!
-My daughter! My daughter!
-Please, sir! No, don't take her, please!
-[Rahila screams] No!
[Ishaya] Mummy, Mummy, Mummy!
Don't follow them!
-[Rahila] Mummy!
-[Ishaya] Don't follow them.
[Oga Rambo in Yoruba] Crazy people,
leave my sight.
[in English] I'll pay you back your money.
Mr. Government, please!
[angrily] You did this… so fix it!
Go look for their money and pay them.
[Patricia] Ishaya,
get out of this house now!
[somber music playing]